Adit Lohani

Kathmandu, Bāgmatī, Nepal

lohaniadit4133@gmail.com

+9779823149600

linkedin.com/in/adit-lohani

Summary

My name is Adit Lohani. |Student|, |Researcher|, |Enthusiast|, |Steminist|. I'm most passionate about giving back to the community and learning new things, and my goal is to change this world towards positivity. In my free time Ilike working on Photoshop and do some open source programming.

Experience



Academic Captain and Deputy School Captain

Budhanilkantha School

Apr 2022 - Present (1 month +)

For the new Academic year of 2079 BS, I am appointed as the Deputy School Captain and Academic Captain. During my tenure, I have planned to conduct various activities with the help from the council. It will be a great opportunity to be the mediator between the students and the school management committee. I have ensured to enact SQ3R, PQ4R, Feynman's Technique and Pomodoro Techniques starting from the junior classes as habits build from an early age. As being the Deputy School captain and an important post holder in the school council, I will organize different programs related to DC, CP. Also, In collaboration with the different clubs, My duty is to conduct various club activities and I will give my best to the best of my abilities. I hope to have a successful tenure.

Mathematics Olympiad Team

OlympEd

Jan 2022 - Present (4 months +)



Projects Department

World Education Criticism Project

Feb 2022 - Present (3 months +)



Mathematics Coordinator

Squad of Physics, Astronomy and Mathematics Learners (SPAM)

Jan 2022 - Present (4 months +)



Student

Budhanilkantha School

May 2016 - Present (6 years +)



Outreach Coordinator

ETWA: Educating the World Association

Jan 2022 - Present (4 months +)



The Curae Organization
Jan 2022 - Present (4 months +)

Education

Budhanilkantha School

SEE, CIE, AS/ A Levels 2016 - 2023

New Summit School Nepal

Class 2 - class 5, NEB May 2012 - Apr 2016

Licenses & Certifications

Covid 19 Contact Tracing - John Hopkins University PDU3QPNQYAZU

United Nations Sustainable Development Goals - Global Goodwill Ambassadors Foundation (GGAF) kpzprepc96

COVID Vaccine Ambassador - The Johns Hopkins University 2CBY4P3AC9S3

Astrometrica - INTERNATIONAL ASTRONOMICAL SEARCH COLLABORATION Pan-STARRS, IASC

Key considerations for SARS-CoV-2 antigen RDT implementation - World Health Organization

xobad-rutoh-togot-cocah-doben

- **COVID-19 Training for Healthcare Workers** Stanford University LRZ6GT6UKH9N
- **################################** Stanford University J68BK9EUUPDV
- Physics 102 Electric Charges and Fields Rice University Electrical and Computer Engineering

- Physics 102 Electric Potential and DC Circuits Rice University Electrical and Computer Engineering
 6MNNCHVHNG8T
- Measuring and Maximizing Impact of COVID-19 Contact Tracing John Hopkins University
 AME6FV5WRYDF
- Strategies for Assisted Living Communities during COVID-19 John Hopkins University
 V57Z8ECH8HC8
- Sleep for Better Mental Health The Knights of Safety™ Academy cu5tbi77e1
- Coping in Isolation: Understanding Depression and Anxiety The Knights of Safety™ Academy mvdjp84ckz
- Building Resilience and Avoiding Burnout The Knights of Safety™ Academy x6g97h0lst
- Understanding Motivation and Motivational Factors The Knights of Safety™
 Academy
 aaov94s2f8
- Self-Care Technique to Reduce Stress The Knights of Safety™ Academy 1jsdmx4lza
- Understanding and Managing Panic Attacks The Knights of Safety™ Academy yzpkh2hplpq
- Mental Health Awareness The Knights of Safety™ Academy akpdojj97z
- Psychological First Aid The Knights of Safety™ Academy pwz5cnqsd9
- Introduction to Electronics Georgia Institute of Technology

- Introduction to Calculus University of Sydney XH9YHNM4V692
- Introduction to Engineering Mechanics Georgia Institute of Technology N46XW52SCJ4E
- Matrix Algebra for Engineers The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology
 HRGQF9VR4F6L
- Electrodynamics: An Introduction Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology

 KXPDAQHN7FD8

Skills

Microsoft PowerPoint • Python (Programming Language) • Adobe Photoshop • Analytical Skills • Project Management • Microsoft Excel • Microsoft Word • HTML • Communication • Leadership

Honors & Awards

National Hero - Science, Technology, Engineering and Mathematics(STEM Nepal), Science Teacher's Association Of Nepal(STAN Nepal) with Nepal Junior Science Olympiad.

Sep 2021

In Nepal Junior Science Olympiad 2021, I was ranked third all over Nepal. Nepal Junior Science Olympiad is a science olympiad organized by STEM and STAN Nepal. Out of the two tests conducted by the STAN, I was placed 3rd (National Hero) with the marks 91 out of total 100. This was a year long olympiad where we were given some online trainings regarding the subject in the mid 2020, during lockdown. After the trainings, we had our first round tests. Out of which 100 people were shortlisted for the next round. After the first round, there was a gap of 8 months for us to self-study and practice with reference to the syllabus. Then after 8 months, we were again called to sit for the Final Round Exam, which was also called "Talent Hunt". This took place on 28th September 2021. I took the test and was declared "National Hero" for my marvelous performance in the test. This accomplishment helped me reflect upon my knowledge and skills in the field of Science. This has encouraged me to participate more and work hard in achieving success. With this program, I feel more confident, determined and it also encourages me to participate and do well in Science in the upcoming future.

1st position at District Mathematics Olympiad - Mathematics Association of Nepal Apr 2021

Ever since I remember, I have had a great interest in mathematics. Even as a five year old, I used to play with numbers in my heads, multiply it divide it and add numbers. Eventually, my interest grew even more

when I started BNKS. Maybe, it was because of our class teacher. I used to participate in many intra and

inter school mathematics competition, but I had never seen any competition like DMC (District Mathematics Competition). The competition was both challenging and fun. In the test, I scored 43 out of 45 and came first in the District Mathematics Competition and this is one of my greatest accomplishments in Maths and I take it as an inspiration to grow and improve further. This has also been my reason to take further maths in Alevels. This also reflects my interest and confidence towards the subject. To sum it up, this competition has always been a source of inspiration to grow and it has helped me be more focused and think intuitively.